<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.ktimer</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ktimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KTimer</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKTimerxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KTimer</name>
  <summary>Countdown Launcher</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Llançador amb compte enrere</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Llançador amb compte arrere</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Spouštěč s odpočtem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Rückwärtszähler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Countdown Launcher</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Lanzador de cuenta atrás</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Atzekoz aurrera zenbatze abiarazlea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Lähtölaskenta</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Lanceur de compte à rebours</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Iniciador de conta atrás</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Lanceator de computo a retro</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Conto alla rovescia</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">카운트다운 실행기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Starter van aftellen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Nedteljingsstartar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Odliczanie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Lançamento Temporizado</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Lançador de contagem regressiva</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Odpočítavané spúšťanie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Nerräknande startprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Таймер</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxCountdown Launcherxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">倒计时执行器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KTimer is a little tool to execute programs after some time. It allows you to enter several tasks and to set a timer for each of them. The timers for each task can be started, stopped, changed, or looped.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KTimer és una petita eina per executar programes després d'un temps determinat. Permet introduir diverses tasques i establir un temporitzador per a cadascuna d'elles. Els comptadors de temps per a cada tasca es poden iniciar, aturar, modificar o repetir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KTimer és una petita eina per executar programes després d'un temps determinat. Permet introduir diverses tasques i establir un temporitzador per a cadascuna d'elles. Els comptadors de temps per a cada tasca es poden iniciar, aturar, modificar o repetir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KTimer ist ein Programm, um andere Anwendungen nach einer bestimmten Zeit zu starten. Es erlaubt das Erfassen von mehreren Aufgaben mit je eigenem Countdown. Jeder einzelne Countdown kann individuell gestartet, angehalten, geändert oder repetiert werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KTimer is a little tool to execute programs after some time. It allows you to enter several tasks and to set a timer for each of them. The timers for each task can be started, stopped, changed, or looped.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KTimer es una pequeña herramienta para ejecutar programas tras cierto tiempo. Le permite introducir varias tareas y definir un temporizador para cada una de ellas. Puede iniciar, detener, modificar o poner en bucle estos temporizadores.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KTimer adierazitako denbora igarotakoan aplikazioak exekutatzeko programa bat da. Hainbat ataza sartu eta bakoitzari atzera zenbatze bat ezarri dakioke. Ataza bakoitzaren atzera zenbatzea abiarazi, gelditu, aldatu edo begiztaz lotu daiteke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KTimer on pieni työkalu ohjelmien ajamiseksi tietyssä ajassa. Voit asettaa useita tehtäviä ja kullekin ajastimen. Kunkin tehtävän ajastimen voi käynnistää, pysäyttää tai sitä voi muuttaa tai asettaa sen silmukkaan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KTimer est un petit outil qui exécute des programmes après un laps de temps défini. Il vous permet de configurer plusieurs tâches et de définir un compte à rebours pour chacune d'entre elles. Il est possible de lancer, d'arrêter, de modifier ou de faire tourner en boucle les comptes à rebours de chaque tâche.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KTimer é unha pequena ferramenta para executar programas despois dun certo tempo. Permítelle introducir varias tarefas e definir unha conta atrás para cada unha delas. As contas atrás de cada tarefa poden iniciarse, deterse, modificarse ou executarse en bucle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KTimer è un piccolo strumento per eseguire i programmi dopo un certo tempo. Ti permette di inserire molte attività e di impostare un temporizzatore per ciascuna di esse; questi possono essere avviati, fermati, modificati o ripetuti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KTimer는 시간을 두고 프로그램을 실행할 수 있는 작은 도구입니다. 여러 작업과 타이머를 지정할 수 있으며, 각각 작업의 타이머를 개별적으로 관리할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KTimer is een klein hulpmiddel om programma's uit te voeren na enige tijd. Het stelt u in staat om verschillende taken in te voeren en een timer voor elk van hen in te stellen. De timers voor elke taak kunnen worden gestart, gestopt, gewijzigd of in een loop gezet worden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KTimer er eit lite verktøy for automatisk start av program når det har gått ei fastsett tid. Du kan leggja til fleire oppgåver og ha ei eiga nedteljing for kvar av dei. Nedteljarane kan du òg starta, stoppa, endra eller køyra i løkkje.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KTimer jest małym narzędziem do wykonywania programów po danym czasie. Umożliwia podanie kliku zadań i ustawienia czasomierza dla nich. Czasomierz dla każdego z zadań można rozpocząć, zatrzymać, zmienić lub zapętlić.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KTimer é uma pequena ferramenta para executar programas ao fim de algum tempo. Permite-lhe introduzir várias tarefas e a definir um cronómetro para cada uma delas. Poderá iniciar, parar, modificar ou configurar em ciclo cada uma das tarefas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KTimer é uma pequena ferramenta para executar programas em um tempo determinado. Permite-lhe inserir diversas tarefas e definir um cronômetro para cada uma delas. Os cronômetros de cada tarefa podem ser iniciados, parados, alterados ou colocados em ciclo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ktimer är ett litet verktyg för att köra program efter en viss tid. Det låter dig ange flera aktiviteter och ställa in en tidtagare för var och en av dem. Tidtagningen av varje aktivitet kan startas, stoppas, ändras eller upprepas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KTimer — невеличка програма для відкладеного запуску інших програм. За її допомогою ви зможете вказати декілька завдань і встановити для кожного з них таймер. Таймери для кожного з завдань можна запускати, зупиняти, змінювати або зациклювати.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKTimer is a little tool to execute programs after some time. It allows you to enter several tasks and to set a timer for each of them. The timers for each task can be started, stopped, changed, or looped.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KTimer 是一个用于在一段时间之后执行程序的小工具。它让您可以创建多个任务，并且为它们每一个设置一个定时器。每个任务的定时器均可被启动、停止、更改或循环运行。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=ktimer</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=ktimer&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=ktimer</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://utils.kde.org/projects/ktimer/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>KTimer configuration window</caption>
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/ktimer.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>ktimer</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.ktimer.desktop</launchable>
</component>
